<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Saylani Welfare</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Enable social recommendations</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Recommendations for people to contact
        based on your message history
    </string>

    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Display name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">John Smith</string>

    <string name="pref_title_add_friends_to_messages">Add friends to messages</string>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_titles">
        <item>Always</item>
        <item>When possible</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Sync frequency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>15 minutes</item>
        <item>30 minutes</item>
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>360</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entries">
        <item>Entry 1</item>
        <item>Entry 2</item>
        <item>Entry 3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entry_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="multi_select_list_preference_default_value" />
    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>
    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>

    <string name="title_activity_sadqa">Sadqa</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about"><font color="black"></font>About</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        <b>"Introduction\n\n"</b>

		"Established in May 1999 by famous spiritual and religious scholar Maulana Bashir Ahmed Farooqui,"
		"Saylani Welfare International Trust was built on the fundamentals of breaking the cycle of"
		"poverty, alleviating the financial troubles of the poor, giving people a chance to live a"
		"dignified life and spreading happiness.\n\n"

		"We are an organization that believes in lighting up the lives of underprivileged people across"
		"the world. We endeavor to provide the best quality services in areas including food, education,"
		"medical and social welfare free of cost to people living in the dark. With over 60 different sectors,\n\n"

		"we feed thousands of hungry people each day, hundreds more are given the hope of life through"
		"medical health care, many are educated to become leaders of tomorrow and several are given the"
		"opportunity to stand on their feet financially.\n\n"

        "Today, we are proud to say that our physical presence extends throughout Pakistan with a vast network"
        "of 125 branches operating in major cities including Karachi, Lahore, Islamabad, Rawalpindi, Hyderabad and"
	    "Faisalabad. Apart from Pakistan, we have overseas offices in the UK, USA and UAE as well. Our worldwide"
	    "branches are operating under the guidance of a team of over 2,000 working professionals who help almost"
	    "125,000 people on a daily basis.\n\n"

        "We strongly believe that a little help goes a long way and our work would not be possible without the "
		"generous support of our valuable donors. Our local and international donors have graciously lent us a hand"
		"by supporting our causes and enabling us to serve the needs of people in need.\n\n"


        "<b>Message from the chairman.\n\n</b>"

        "<i>Assalam-o-Alaikum</i>\n\n"

        "<i>Who is it that would loan Allah a goodly loan so He may multiply it for him many times over? ( Surat Baqara, Verse 245)</i>\n\n"

        "It should be noted that Allah, who is in need of no one and nothing, instills upon his men to give Qarz-e-Hasana because it is"
		"in man’s nature to be frugal whilst spending his wealth. Allah speaks about qarz because it is returned and Allah promises that"
		"He will return the goodly loan by 70 folds. Allah conveys his message to the Muslim ummah through the Holy Prophet Muhammad"
		"prompting Muslims to spend their wealth in a certain way. He says,Oh children of Adam! Trust me with your wealth."
		"If you do so, no fire, flood or thieves will be able to rob you off your money. Instead, you will be endowed with your wealth"
		"when you most need it. He further says that the poor and weak will not remain hungry and naked except due to the"
        "negligence ofthe rich, who should not be stingy in spending their money on those worse off than themselves."
        "Allah will not only take strict accountability from those people but He will also punish them accordingly. "
        "On the Day Of Judgement, the rich will be humiliated\n\n"

		"because they did not help the needy. The needy will complain to Allah and say that all those men on whom you graciously bestowed"
		"the rights of wealth showed negligence in its proper use; they were busy spending on themselves and forgot about us, the ones"
		"who needed it. Allah will reply to this and say: “I swear on my respect and glory! I will bring you closer to me"
		"and push them further away.”\n\n"


    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_aqiqa">Aqiqa</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact">Contact</string>

    <string name="message_string">Please fill in all the required details</string>

    
    <string name="send_to">Share</string>

</resources>
